

Raj Kale

Software Engineer

I am a 20 years old energetic undergraduate student studying Computer Science at Army Institute of Technology. Since technology is a boon in today's world, with upgrading systems I keep upgrading myself in order to keep a technical modularity.

kale44772@gmail.com

8888228947



Pune, India

EDUCATION

Computer Science

Army Institute of Technology, Pune University

07/2019 - Present

Diploma in Computer Science Jaihind Polytechnic, Junnar

06/2016 - 05/2019

Junnar, Pune

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Video Conferencing Web App using Node and React is

- Socket.io
- Peer is
- Express

E commerce application using React js

- Redux Context API
- Stripe Payment
- Firebase Cloud Firestore
- Material UI

Spotify, Netflix, Airbnb Clone using React is

- REST API
- Context API

Grocery E commerce App in Flutter with Admin Panel

Firebase

Blooming Souls Android App

- App to provide Courses, Academic Mentoring and Life Coaching.
- Implemented using Google Firebase Database and Storage.
- Supports Google and Facebook and Email Authentication.

Music Genre Classification

Developed in React and Django Framework

WORK EXPERIENCE

App Development Internship Blooming Souls Pvt. Ltd.

09/2020 - Present

In-Plant Trainee College Level

04/2018 - 05/2018

SKILLS



CERTIFICATES

State Level Engineering Talent Search Examination

LANGUAGES

Marathi

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

English

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Outdoor Sports especially Cricket

Geographic Locations